Sreelatha Vallabhaneni

Full-Stack Developer and Software Tester

I am an energetic and imaginative young web and Mobile app developer, passionate about creating user friendly and responsive applications while being motivated to learn new technologies at a fast pace. proven experience and success working as a software test engineer as an individual and team member. comprehensive talents across the design development, testing, debugging and documentation of applications.



- xreelatha.vallabhaneni@gmail.com
- P Høje-Taastrup, Denmark
- in linkedin.com/in/sreelatha-vallabhaneni-37a406b9
- 71665956
- sreelatha-portfolio.netlify.app/
- github.com/Sreelatha-Vallabhaneni

EDUCATION / TRAINING

Masters in Signal Processing Blekinge Institute of Technology

01/2010 - 01/2012

Karlskrona, Sweden

Full-Stack Developer

HackYourFuture-Copenhagen

08/2019 - 05/2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

React Native Developer

Freetrailer

03/2021 - 03/2021

Copenhagen, Denmark.

Frontend Developer winefamly

09/2020 - 11/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

Achievements / Tasks

 Connected React JS to Magento 2, developed some parts (like Add to cart, productList, Product Rate, Comments / Reviews, etc ...) in website with ReactJS to improve the speed, used webPackage, NPM Package, and reduced bundle size, Adding Widgets in Magento admin, Fixed Responsive styling, Participated in Daily / weekly meetings (Fx: Daily-Task, Task Grooming, stand-up, company Info, etc ..), etc ...

Software Tester

Mavininfotech

04/2014 - 09/2014 Hyderabad, India

Software Tester

LiveTech

03/2013 - 03/2014

Hvderabad, India

SKILLS



FINAL PROJECT

Dashboard App (seasony.dk). (2020) 🗗

 Developed a Dashboard App for visualizing sensor data from plants and a collaboration between HackYourFuture-CPH and seasony.dk, which is a startup specializing in vertical farming with robotics. It is Full-Stack application using ReactJS, Hooks, Storybook, Swagger for API documentation, NodeJS, KnexJS, MYSQL, ESLint, Prettier, Recharts, Firebase, Git, Github, Heroku etc...

CERTIFICATES

ISTQB Certificate

test in Danish 2 (PD2)

LANGUAGES

Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Profesion

Danish

Limited Working Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Swedish

Elementary Proficiency